A Guide to the Thomas Miller Papers, 1773-1852
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Thomas Miller Papers, 1773-1852
The Library of Virginia
Barcode numbers 1147142-1147154/Goochland County (Va.) Reels 122-139
5.75 cu. ft.; 18 microfilm reels
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from Goochland County Circuit Court under the accession number 38114.
Microfilm reels were generated by Backstage Library Works in 2010 through the Library of Virginia's Circuit Court Records Program.
Biographical/Historical Information
Thomas Miller was born in Goochland County, Virginia on 20 March 1754. He was the son of William Miller and Mary Heath. He was an attorney, deputy sheriff and sheriff of Goochland County, a member of the Virginia House of Delegates, and a planter with estates in Goochland, Spotsylvania, and King William Counties. He married Constance Massie, the daughter of Maj. Nathaniel Massie and Betsy Watkins. Thomas Miller died at his residence Lavallie in Goochland County on 27 April 1819.
James B. Ferguson was one of Thomas Miller's executors. He was born circa 1781, and was also a planter and member of the Virginia House of Delegates. He married Sally Gay, the daughter of Willam Gay and Judith Scott.
Scope and Content Information
Papers, 1754-1819, of Thomas Miller (1754-1819) of Goochland County, Virginia, as well as the executor of his estate James B. Ferguson (b. ca. 1781), also of Goochland. Includes correspondence, subject files, accounts, receipts, papers of William Gay and William Pope, and oversize items. This collection is part of the Goochland County Circuit Court Records.
The correspondence covers the years 1781-1848 and is divided into letters to and from Thomas Miller, and those to and from James B. Ferguson. Topics covered in the Thomas Miller letters mainly concern business matters relating to the operation of his vast land holdings in Goochland, Spotsylvania, and King William Counties, and his various plantations, including Byrd, Lavallie, Manskin Lodge, Slab City, and Woodville. Subjects include the purchase, sale, and shipments of corn, wheat, flour, and timber produced on his plantations, as well as the sale and hire of slaves to work the land. Many of these letters are written by the overseers of his properties.
A large proportion of the letters are financial in nature as well, and deal with his acting as security for loans, as well as the loaning of money himself, to various individuals. There are orders for payments of money and for goods. There are letters from brokerage and mercantile houses in Richmond, including Gallego, Richard & Company and Lewis Perkins & Company, which sold Miller's products, and also advanced him his needed capital.
Thomas Miller was an attorney, and many of his letters deal with his duties representing various clients, including notices of his intention to take depositions in court cases. Miller was also deputy sheriff and sheriff of Goochland County. There are a few letters relating to his duties in these positions, including the issuing of executions.
Likewise, the letters of James B. Ferguson are business and financial in nature. Many of them are written by Miller's sons, who inherited their father's estate after his death. James B. Ferguson was one of Miller's executors. There are also many letters from Joseph S. Watkins, with whom Ferguson had numerous business dealings. There is also a letter from Watkins detailing his candidacy for the Virginia House of Delegates in 1832.
The estate papers concern the estates of Obediah Daniel, Gideon Hatcher, Thomas Miller, John Salmon, and Matthew Vaughan. Material found in this series includes accounts, attorneys', clerks' and sheriffs' fee bills, bonds, correspondence, fifas, receipts, sales, and suit papers.
The subject files contain a variety of material, including advertisements, affidavits and depositions, agreements, bonds, clerks' and sheriffs' fee bills, deeds, fifas, various lists, powers of attorney, promissory notes, slave bills of sale, suit papers, and other items. There are also files, interfiled in this series alphabetically by name, for individuals with whom Miller had extensive business dealings.
There are series containing accounts and receipts, both arranged by year. Within the receipts series is a group of receipts for Miller's wheat crop.
There are two series of personal papers of William Gay (1745-1815) and William Pope. Gay's daughter Sally married James B. Ferguson. His papers include accounts, a bond, clerks' fee bills, correspondence, deeds, promissory notes, receipts and a tax bill. The material is business-related, much of it between Gay and John Tabb (1736-1798) of Amelia County. The William Pope papers include accounts, attorney's fees, correspondence, powers of attorney, and suit papers. The majority of these papers relate to William Pope's activities as attorney for Col. John Syme (1727-1805) of Rocky Mills, Hanover County.
The series of oversize items includes accounts, deeds, inventories and appraisements of the estate of Thomas Miller, a lease, lists of judgments recovered against Thomas Miller's executors, and suit papers.
Arrangement
I. Correspondence. II. Estate Papers. III. Subject Files. IV. Accounts V. Receipts. VI. William Gay Papers. VII. William Pope Papers. VIII. Oversize.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
See also Goochland County Judgments at the Library of Virginia for civil suits that involved Thomas Miller.
See also Goochland County Chancery Causes available on the Chancery Records Index at the Library of Virginia web site for chancery suits that involved Thomas Miller and his estate.
Index Terms
Persons:
Daniel, Obediah, d. 1790.; Ferguson, James B., ca. 1781-; Gay, William, 1745-1815.; Hatcher, Gideon, d. 1807.; Miller, Thomas, 1754-1819.; Pope, William.; Salmon, John, d. ca. 1799.; Syme, John, 1727-1805.; Tabb, John, 1736-1798.; Vaughan, Matthew, d. ca. 1799.; Watkins, Joseph S.
Family Names:
Miller family.
Corporate Names:
Gallego, Richard and Company (Richmond, Va.); Lewis Perkins and Company (Richmond, Va.)
Subjects:
African Americans -- History.; Plantation owners -- Virginia -- Goochland County.; Plantations -- Virginia -- Goochland County.; Plantations -- Virginia -- King William County.; Plantations -- Virginia -- Spotsylvania County.; Slaves -- Virginia.
Geographical Names:
Goochland County (Va.) -- History -- 18th century.; Goochland County (Va.) -- History -- 19th century.
Genre and Form Terms:
Accounts.; Agreements.; Bonds.; Deeds -- Virginia -- Goochland County.; Estate administration records -- Virginia -- Goochland County.; Financial records.; Judicial records.; Letters (correspondence); Personal papers.; Promissory notes.; Receipts.
Contents List
- Correspondence
  The correspondence covers the years 1781-1848 and is divided into letters to and from Thomas Miller, and those to and from James B. Ferguson. Topics covered in the Thomas Miller letters mainly concern business matters relating to the operation of his vast land holdings in Goochland, Spotsylvania, and King William Counties, and his various plantations, including Byrd, Lavallie, Manskin Lodge, Slab City, and Woodville. Subjects include the purchase, sale, and shipments of corn, wheat, flour, and timber produced on his plantations, as well as the sale and hire of slaves to work the land. Many of these letters are written by the overseers of his properties. A large proportion of the letters are financial in nature as well, and deal with his acting as security for loans, as well as the loaning of money himself, to various individuals. There are orders for payments of money and for goods. There are letters from brokerage and mercantile houses in Richmond, including Gallego, Richard & Company and Lewis Perkins & Company, which sold Miller's products, and also advanced him his needed capital. Thomas Miller was an attorney, and many of his letters deal with his duties representing various clients, including notices of his intention to take depositions in court cases. Miller was also deputy sheriff and sheriff of Goochland County. There are a few letters relating to his duties in these positions, including the issuing of executions. Likewise, the letters of James B. Ferguson are business and financial in nature. Many of them are written by Miller's sons, who inherited their father's estate after his death. James B. Ferguson was one of Miller's executors. There are also many letters from Joseph S. Watkins, with whom Ferguson had numerous business dealings. There is also a letter from Watkins detailing his candidacy for the Virginia House of Delegates in 1832.
  - Thomas Miller
    - 1781 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1782 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1783 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1784 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1786 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1787 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1788 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1789 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1790 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1791 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1792 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1793 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1794 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1795 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1796 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1797 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1798 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1799 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1800 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1801 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1802 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1803 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1804 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 1805 (January-July) (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 1805 (August-December) (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1806 (January-June) (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 1806 (July-December) (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 1807 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 1808 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1809 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1810 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1810 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1811 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 1812 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1813 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 1814 (January-August) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 1814 (September-December) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 1815 (January-June) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1815 (July-December) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1816 (January-July) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1816 (August-December) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1817 (January-June) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1817 (July-December) (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1818 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1819 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - James B. Ferguson
    - 1805 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1819 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 1820 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 1821 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 1822 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 1823 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1824 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 1825 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 1826 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 1827 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 1828 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 1829 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1830 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1831 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 1832 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 1833 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - 1834 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 1835 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 1836 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 1838 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1839 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 1840, 1842, 1848 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - n.d. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Estate Papers
  The estate papers concern the estates of Obediah Daniel, Gideon Hatcher, Thomas Miller, John Salmon, and Matthew Vaughan. Material found in this series includes accounts, attorneys', clerks' and sheriffs' fee bills, bonds, correspondence, fifas, receipts, sales, and suit papers.
  - Daniel, Obediah
    - (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hatcher, Gideon
    - Accounts (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Attorney's Fees (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Clerk's Fees (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Court Orders for Payment of Witnesses (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Fifas (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Power of Attorney (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Receipts (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Sheriff's Fees (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Miller, Thomas (see also oversize)
    - Accounts (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
    - Bond (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Clerk's and Sheriff's Fees (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Final Settlement of Accounts (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Receipts (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Sales of Negroes (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Suit Papers (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Salmon, John
    - (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Vaughan, Matthew
    - Accounts and Receipts (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Affidavits and Depositions (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Bonds (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Fifas (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Suit Papers (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Subject Files
  The subject files contain a variety of material, including advertisements, affidavits and depositions, agreements, bonds, clerks' and sheriffs' fee bills, deeds, fifas, various lists, powers of attorney, promissory notes, slave bills of sale, suit papers, and other items. There are also files, interfiled in this series alphabetically by name, for individuals with whom Miller had extensive business dealings.
  - Advertisements for Sales of Property (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Affidavits and Depositions (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Agreements, 1780-1805 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Agreements, 1806-1810 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Agreements, 1811-1815 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Agreements, 1816-1819, 1841 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Appeal Bonds, 1801, 1808 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bail Bond, 1783 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bill of Lading, 1816 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bills of Sale (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bonds, 1782-1799 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Bonds, 1800-1805 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bonds, 1806-1825 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bonds for Slave Hires (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Archibald Bryce & Co. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Capias (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Clerk's Fee Bills (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Davis, Augustine (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Deane, Francis B. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Deane, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Deeds, 1788-1815 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Deeds, 1816-1830 (see also oversize) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Distilled Spirits Inspection Certificate, 1791 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Duke, Edmond (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Ellis & Allen (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
  - Eppes, Francis (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Executors Bond (copy), 1796 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fee Book, 1785-1787 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fifas (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fleming, William R. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fowler, Jacob B. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Forbes, Jesse (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Freeman, Zachariah (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Fuzmore, Isaac Jr. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - George, William (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Horse Pedigree, 1833 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Leake, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Lists of Hands Collecting Bark and Amounts Paid, 1815 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Lists of Negroes (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - List of Prices for Blacksmith Work, 1784 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Lists of Tools and Stock (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Lovell, Micajah (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Lyle, James (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - McBride, Minor (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - McKeand, Willis (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Memoranda (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Morris, Richard (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mutual Assurance Society (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Opinions (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Orders for Payment of Witnesses (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Parrish, Moses (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Poindexter, William G. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pollock, John (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Powers of Attorney (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Promissory Notes, 1782-1794 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Promissory Notes, 1795-1810 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Promissory Notes, 1811-1816 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Promissory Notes, 1817-1839 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Protests (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Riddle, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Royster, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Sheriff's Fee Bills (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Slave Bills of Sale (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Slave Runaways (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Subpoena (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Subscription List, 1830 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Suit Papers - Drumwright vs. Vaughan & Miller (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Suit Papers - Freeman vs. Miller (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Suit Papers - Houchins vs. Miller (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Suit Papers - Richardson vs. Toler (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Suit Papers - Miscellaneous (see also oversize) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Tax Receipts (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Will (portion, unidentified) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Woodson, Joseph (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Accounts (see also oversize)
  Contains accounts arranged by year.
  - 1773 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1782 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1783 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1785 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1786 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1787 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1788 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1789 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1790 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1791 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1792 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 1793 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1794 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1795 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1796 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1797 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1798 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1799 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1800 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1801 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1802 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1803 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1804 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1805 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 1806 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 1807 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 1808 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1809 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1810 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1811 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1812 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1813 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1814 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1815 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 1816 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 1817 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 1818 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 1819 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 1820-1829 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 1834, 1852 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - n.d. (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Receipts
  Contains receipts arranged by year. Within the receipts series is a group of receipts for Miller's wheat crop.
  - General Receipts
    - 1781 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 1782 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 1783 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1784 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1785 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 1786 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 1787 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1788 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1789 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 1790 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 1791 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 1792 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 1793 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 1794 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 1795 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 1796 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - 1798 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 1799 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 1800 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 1801 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 1802 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - 1803 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - 1804 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - 1805 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - 1806 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - 1807 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - 1808 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - 1809 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - 1810 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - 1811 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - 1812 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - 1813 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - 1814 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - 1815 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - 1816 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - 1817 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - 1818 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - 1819 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - 1820 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - 1821 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - 1822 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - 1823 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - 1826 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - n.d. (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Receipts for Wheat Crop
    - 1782 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 1783 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 1788 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 1789 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 1791 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 1792 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - 1793 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - 1796 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - 1799 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 1800 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - 1803 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 1804 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - 1805 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - 1806 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - 1807 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 1808 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - 1809 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - 1810 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - 1811 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - 1812 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - 1813 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - 1815 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - 1816 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - 1817 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - 1818 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - 1820 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- William Gay Papers
  There is a series of personal papers of William Gay (1745-1815). Gay's daughter Sally married James B. Ferguson. His papers include accounts, a bond, clerks' fee bills, correspondence, deeds, promissory notes, receipts and a tax bill. The material is business-related, much of it between Gay and John Tabb (1736-1798) of Amelia County.
  - Accounts (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Bond (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Clerk's Fee Bill (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1779-1788 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1789-1807 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Deeds (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Promissory Notes (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Receipts (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Tax Bill (Box 12, Folder 9)
- William Pope Papers
  The William Pope papers include accounts, attorney's fees, correspondence, powers of attorney, and suit papers. The majority of these papers relate to William Pope's activities as attorney for Col. John Syme (1727-1805) of Rocky Mills, Hanover County.
  - Accounts (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Accounts (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Powers of Attorney (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Suit Papers (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Oversize
  The series of oversize items includes accounts, deeds, inventories and appraisements of the estate of Thomas Miller, a lease, lists of judgments recovered against Thomas Miller's executors, and suit papers.
  - Accounts (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - Deed (Goochland County), 1815 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Deed (King William County), 1817 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Inventories and Appraisements, Estate of Thomas Miller (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
  - Lease (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Lists of Judgments Recovered Against Thomas Miller's Executors (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Suit Papers - Miller vs. Ferguson, Bill, 1826 (Box 13, Folder 8)